Search 

            ### [How to know if I’m Allergic to Cats](https://healthstoday.com/how-to-know-if-im-allergic-to-cats/ "How to know if I’m Allergic to Cats")

            ### [Let’s Get Nutty With Allergies](https://healthstoday.com/lets-get-nutty-with-allergies/ "Let’s Get Nutty With Allergies")

            ### [Daily Showers- Are They Good Or Bad For The Immune System?](https://healthstoday.com/daily-showers-are-they-good-or-bad-for-the-immune-system/ "Daily Showers- Are They Good Or Bad For The Immune System?")

            ### [How to know if I have an Egg allergy](https://healthstoday.com/how-to-know-if-i-have-an-egg-allergy/ "How to know if I have an Egg allergy")

            ### [How to avoid pollen allergy](https://healthstoday.com/how-to-avoid-pollen-allergy/ "How to avoid pollen allergy")

Sign in

Welcome! Log into your account

your username

your password

Password recovery

Recover your password

your email

A password will be e-mailed to you.

Advertisement

[Home](https://healthstoday.com/) Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

﻿Last revised: April 10, 2023  

Privacy Policy for HealthsToday  

Privacy Policy for HealthsToday
===============================

At HealthsToday we are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, and disclose information about you when you use our iOS application (the “App”).

Information We Collect
----------------------

When you use the App, we may collect information about you, including:

* Information you provide: We may collect information that you provide to us when you use the App, such as your name, email address, and other contact information.
* Usage information: We may collect information about how you use the App, including the features you use, the pages you visit, and the actions you take.
* Device information: We may collect information about the device you use to access the App, including the hardware model, operating system and version, and mobile network information.
* Cookie information: We may use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about how you use the App, to remember your preferences, and to personalize your experience.

How We Use Your Information
---------------------------

We may use the information we collect for various purposes, including:

* Providing and improving the App: We may use your information to provide and improve the App, to understand how users interact with the App, and to personalize your experience.
* Communicating with you: We may use your information to communicate with you about the App, to respond to your inquiries, and to send you updates and other information about our products and services.
* Advertising and analytics: We may use your information to show you targeted advertising and to perform analytics to help us understand how our advertising is performing.
* Compliance with legal obligations: We may use your information to comply with legal obligations, such as responding to subpoenas or other legal requests.

How We Share Your Information
-----------------------------

We may share your information with third parties, including:

* Service providers: We may share your information with third-party service providers who perform services on our behalf, such as hosting the App, analyzing data, and providing customer support.
* Advertising partners: We may share your information with advertising partners to show you targeted advertising.
* Analytics providers: We may share your information with analytics providers to perform analytics to help us understand how our advertising is performing.
* Other users: We may share your information with other users of the App, such as when you participate in social features of the App.
* Compliance with legal obligations: We may share your information to comply with legal obligations, such as responding to subpoenas or other legal requests.

Your Choices
------------

You may have choices about how we use and share your information, such as:

* Cookies: You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of the App may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
* Promotional Communications: You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by following the instructions in those communications.

Children’s Privacy
==================

The App is not intended for children under 13 years of age, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on the App or on or through any of its features. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.

Changes to This Privacy Policy
==============================

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email (if you have provided us with your email address) or by posting a notice on the App prior to the effective date of the changes.

Advertisement

In our portal you will find content of various kinds: diseases and treatments, well-being, natural remedies, diets and recipes, psychology, couples, motherhood and lifestyle.

Contact us: [HealthsToday.com@gmail.com](mailto:HealthsToday.com@gmail.com)

#### POPULAR POSTS

### [Healthy dog food what to know?](https://healthstoday.com/healthy-dog-food-what-to-know/ "Healthy dog food what to know?")

### [how long does a bathroom remodel take](https://healthstoday.com/how-long-does-a-bathroom-remodel-take/ "how long does a bathroom remodel take")

### [Why keeping your home gutters in good condition is important](https://healthstoday.com/why-keeping-your-home-gutters-in-good-condition-is-important/ "Why keeping your home gutters in good condition is important")

#### POPULAR CATEGORY

© Copyright 2024 - HealthsToday.com

We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies.  

Do not sell my personal information.

Cookie settingsACCEPT

Privacy & Cookies Policy

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.

Non-necessary

 Non-necessary

Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.

SAVE & ACCEPT
